<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.jennic.sdk.zbpro.external.feature"
      label="NXP ZBPro Configuration Editor"
      version="2.0.0"
      provider-name="NXP">

   <description url="http://www.nxp.com">
      Provides support for the development of application software
using NXP wireless microcontrollers and ZigBee PRO wireless
networking stack.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright NXP B.V. 2015-2016 All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      This software is owned by NXP B.V. and/or its supplier and is protected
  under applicable copyright laws. All rights are reserved. We grant You,
  and any third parties, a license to use this software solely and
  exclusively on NXP products [NXP Microcontrollers such as JN514x,JN516x, JN517x]. 
  You, and any third parties must reproduce the copyright and warranty notice 
  and any other legend of ownership on each  copy or partial copy of the software.
 
  THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS &quot;AS IS&quot;  
  AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
  IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE 
  ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE 
  LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR 
  CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF 
  SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS 
  INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN 
  CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) 
  ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE 
  POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. 
 
  Copyright NXP B.V. 2016. All rights reserved
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="NXP ZBPro Eclipse Update Site" url="http://eclipse.nxp.com/update-site"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="com.jennic.zps.configeditor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.jennic.zps.configeditor.edit"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.jennic.zps.configeditor.editor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
