<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.nxp.bsn.jmp.feature"
      label="NXP JN51xx Programmer"
      version="1.1.0.201508141336"
      provider-name="NXP"
      os="win32,linux"
      
      >

   <description>
      NXP JN51xx Flash Programmer
   </description>

   <copyright>
      NXP Laboratories 2014
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      IMPORTANT: Before installing this software carefully read the
following terms and conditions. This Software End-User License
Agreement is a binding agreement between you, the end-user, and
NXP B.V. regarding the use of the software accompanying this
Agreement, which includes computer software, source code and
provided documentation (together &quot;SOFTWARE&quot;). By installing,
copying or otherwise using the SOFTWARE, you agree to be bound
by the terms of this Agreement. 
End User License Agreement
THIS SOFTWARE IS THE PROPERTY OF NXP B.V. (hereinafter referred
to as ”NXP”), and COPYRIGHT NXP  2012, ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES IS THIS SOFTWARE OR ANY DERIVATIVE WORKS
THEREOF TO BE EXPOSED TO OR PLACED UNDER AN OPEN SOURCE LICENSE
OF ANY TYPE WITHOUT THE EXPRESSED WRITTEN PERMISSION OF NXP B.V.
1. Object and scope of the agreement
This SOFTWARE is made available by NXP for the following purposes
only:
a) to install all components of the SOFTWARE on a hard disk or
other storage medium or on a network fileserver; 
b) to create backup copies of the SOFTWARE; 
c) to install and use the SOFTWARE in-house;
d) to modify the source code and create derivative works thereof;
e) to develop, sell, distribute or otherwise dispose of applications
based on the source code.
Neither the SOFTWARE, the source code of the SOFTWARE nor the
source code of any derivative works thereof may be distributed
to any third party without the prior written permission of NXP.
The SOFTWARE and any derivative works thereof may only be used
in conjunction with devices that are developed, produced, sold
and marketed to be used with Wireless Microcontroller  ICs and
network stacks manufactured by NXP or under license of NXP. 
“Wireless Microcontroller ICs and network stacks” shall mean
any of the following: JN5148; JN5142; JN5139; JN5121; JenNet;
JenNet-IP.]
Nothing in this agreement shall be construed as the grant of
a license under any patent or patent application or other intellectual
property rights owned or controlled by NXP.
2. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES: 
YOU AGREE THAT NXP HAS MADE NO EXPRESS WARRANTIES TO YOU REGARDING
THE SOFTWARE AND THAT THE SOFTWARE IS BEING PROVIDED TO YOU &quot;AS
IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.
NXP DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO THE SOFTWARE, EXPRESS
OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES
OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, MERCHANTABILITY, MERCHANTABLE
QUALITY OR NONINFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS.
Some states or jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied
warranties so the above limitations or parts of it may apply
only to the extent legally permitted to you.
3. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY: 
IN NO EVENT WILL NXP BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS OF USE, INTERRUPTION
OF BUSINESS, OR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND (INCLUDING LOST PROFITS) REGARDLESS
OF THE FORM OF ACTION WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE),
STRICT PRODUCT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF END-USER HAS BEEN
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
Some states or jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation
of incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation,
exclusion or parts of it may apply only to the extent legally
permitted to you.
4. USAGE
ANY SOFTWARE MADE AVAILABLE IN FORM OF THIS PACKAGE IS MADE AVAILABLE
FOR USE BY END USERS ONLY AND ANY FURTHER COPYING, REPRODUCTION
OR REDISTRIBUTION OF THIS PACKAGE OR PARTS OF IT IS EXPRESSLY
PROHIBITED. WE DO NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED WILL
MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR THAT THE OPERATION WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED
OR ERROR FREE. THEY ARE NOT OPTIMISED IN TERMS OF SPEED OR SIZE.
THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF USE IS ASSUMED
BY YOU.
You are expressly prohibited from using the SOFTWARE in the operation
of nuclear facilities, in aircraft navigation. in aircraft communication,
in aircraft control in military, aircraft, space or life support
equipment, nor in applications where failure or malfunction of
the SOFTWARE can reasonably be expected to result in personal
injury, death or severe property or environmental damage.
5. Third Parties (Including Open Source)
The Use of this Software may require You to respect the rights
of other third parties, including but not exclusively, GNU General
Public License and the ZigBee Alliance. NXP is not responsible
and shall not be held responsible in any manner for Your failure
to seek licenses and respect the rights of third parties.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime" version="3.9.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui" version="3.105.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.nxp.bsn.jmp.win32"
         os="win32"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.1.0.201508141336"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.nxp.bsn.jmp.linux"
         os="linux"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.nxp.bsn.jmp.launch"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.0.201508141336"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.nxp.bsn.launch.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.0.201508141336"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.nxp.bsn.jmp.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.1.0.201508141336"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
